(Penny:)Oh, it would be great
to practice on a real doctor.
(Emily:)Yeah. I'm sure that'd be fine.
(Sheldon:)I have some odd
freckles on my buttocks.
(Sheldon:)Can I make an appointment
for you to look at them?
(Emily:)Um... okay, I guess.
(Amy:)I'm with him three
years, nothing.
She's with two minutes, and
he's taking his pants off.
(Bernadette:)Last night was fun.
What did you think of Emily?
(Penny:)I don't know.
(Penny:)I kind of got the sense
she didn't like me.
Did she say she didn't like you?
(Penny:)Of course not. No one ever says
(Penny:)they don't like you
straight to your face.
(Amy:)We have led different lives.
(Bernadette:)You guys just met.
Why would she feel that way?
(Penny:)It's just this
vibe I got.
(Bernadette:)I'm sure you're worried
about nothing.
Yeah.
(Penny:)You're probably right.
(Penny:)I used to think
my high school P.E. teacher
(Penny:)didn't like me,
but it turned out,
(Penny:)she liked me a little too much.
(Bernadette:)Really?
Yeah.
(Penny:)It was fine.
(Penny:)We went to a Melissa Etheridge
concert, I got an A,